This is Daryn from the Philippines.
I am a video editor and a little bit something about myself is that
a little background is that I have 10 years experience in graphics design and
then, uh, a transition.
into video editing because, uh,
we, it got a trend that transform,
uh, video was, uh, the format that is trending and what is,
uh, really, uh, making or taking the attention of the people right now.
And then, uh, cause I want to upscale.
And I, uh, want to learn,
like I have a motto and I, uh,
do with, uh, follow James Clear,
which is the author of, uh,
Atomic Habits, which is, uh, 1% Better Every Day.
So yeah, I, uh, I strive to learn new things every day,
which is, uh, which is aligned to the career path that I want to
be, which is, uh, creative strategist, not just a video editor.
So that's why I am studying right now,
uh, the e-comm talent, uh,
by the Carlo, of course, for a video editor who wants to learn
how direct response work and how,
uh, videos convert and make revenues,
which is, uh, what, like,
the client wanted, right? Either. Sales are,
like, they are going to funnel leads,
so, uh, that's what, uh, the pain point of the clients,
right? And I want to, uh,
give value, and I want to help, uh,
to solve that problem. So,
yeah. Because we have a, uh, limited time,
uh, let's just talk how, uh, what is my AI workflow.
So, as you can see here, I have a ad,
which is a 15-second ad. Uh, what I did here is,
uh, because I want to practice, like, uh, AI,
uh, editing from, uh, scratch, like,
I just have a product, uh, image,
and then an avatar, which is from Pinterest,
which is AI, as you can see here, uh,
here, uh, avatar, this is the avatar,
and then, uh, uh,
just to Ooh. Uh,
minimized copyright issue, I, uh,
made this avatar, which is, I have here a gem in Gemini,
which is, uh, making a portrait of,
uh, girl, which is,
uh, you just, uh, give the prom a young woman in her early 30s,
just with long, voluminous, dark brown hair.
And then it give me the prom here,
uh, advanced prom engineering, uh,
cause we want UGC style, right?
Uh, we want it, like, uh, organic.
So, shot on iPhone. Handheld phone, portrait,
vertical, social media, like, stuff like that.
Then I'll just put here in either Fall or Higgs field,
uh, to generate the avatar or,
yeah, as you can see here. And then,
uh, this is the avatar. And then,
uh, I wanted to, like, recreate this scene.
So what I did is, in Gemini,
I have this gem, which is a scene builder,
uh, to, uh, get the prompt.
And then, what I did is, it's loading,
uh, I just put the image here.
Then, uh, it gave me the,
uh, prompt that I sh- I should put in here in,
uh, ByteDance, uh, Cdream.
Like, image to image to image,
cause, uh, we, we wanted to,
like, uh, Cdream,
or Banana, uh, like,
image to image, cause we want to put this avatar as a reference,
and then, uh, I put this, so this,
as you can see, this,
and this avatar to this, as you can see.
And then, after that, I,
I, so I generated,
alright, so the video,
here, video file,
so this is the, the first,
you know how you always run out of video? Your favorite shampoo.
See, so this is, I'll show, just show you the ad first.
You know how you always run out of your favorite shampoo?
And you're like, oh gosh, I'm gonna restock.
Well that's why Monday made jumbo sizes of your shampoo and your conditioner.
Last time. It's triple the amount of time,
quadruple, depends on how often you wash your hair,
of course. This is, uh, like,
generated, uh, from scratch and zero,
as you can see here, right? So yeah,
uh, five minutes. So this is the,
like, this is, like, the woman in grocery,
I just put it there, then I prompted, like,
uh, make this woman and then change the face.
So yeah, that's it. Like, that's how,
yeah, I have, uh, experience.